http://www.butyoudontlooksick.com/about/privacy-policy/

Baby Boomers/ 50+/ Seniors
But You Don't Look Sick?
Digestive Disorders
Doctors and Hospitals, etc.
Having a Bad Day / Venting
Headaches, Migraines, etc.
Healthy Weight Management
Heart Conditions inc Dysautonomia
In the News…
Infertility and Health Related Fertility Issues.
Invisible Diseases
Links, Awards and More!
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.butyoudontlooksick.com/terms-of-use.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.butyoudontlooksick.com
388 2nd Avenue
Massapequa Park, NY 11762
USA
[email protected]
Comments are closed.
Welcome to ButYouDontLookSick.com
Sign up for our FREE Newsletter
RSS feed
Twitter
BYDLS on Facebook
Christine on Facebook
MySpace
LinkedIn
Spoon Lady SpeaksMay 12 is International Fibromyalgia Awareness Day!In addition to my lupus, I also have fibromyalgia. One of my best friends was recently diagnosed with it as well. I love her. I feel that although pain and fibro is something I know a bit about, I can not help her acceptance of this diagnosis. I have seen ...More: May 12 is International Fibromyalgia Awareness Day!May 10th is Lupus Awareness Day! Have you loved someone with Lupus lately?Wear orange or purple, send friends your favorite awareness websites (bydls.com ? lol) to educate, read, ask your friends to read some lupus facts, make your status a lupus support or awareness message, blog about lupus, blog about your friends with lupus, Do something nice for a person living with ...More: May 10th is Lupus Awareness Day! Have you loved someone with Lupus lately?After saying hello to my guests, I say #hellokeurig and feel like the perfect hostDon’t Be Afraid of the Paper Directions!
So much paper packing In the box and such a thick instruction book. All those languages, I only speak English. I have to guess you are trying to hide the best secret in the world: that the new 550 is EASY to use. I ...More: After saying hello to my guests, I say #hellokeurig and feel like the perfect hostI made a healthy little switch to Musselman's Applesauce. Small diet changes can make a big difference.How lucky is this? In the mail today, I received a free sample of Musselman’s Apple Sauce, just when I made a commitment to lose weight last week. The great god of internet says I can snack on ½ cup of unsweetened apple sauce for 2 points but with a ...More: I made a healthy little switch to Musselman's Applesauce. Small diet changes can make a big difference.
Popular Posts
The Spoon Theory written by Christine MiserandinoPlease take the time to read Christine Miserandino's personal story and analogy of what it is like to live with sickness...Sick Humor: The top ten worst suggestions commonly given to someone with a chronic illnessSometimes you just gotta have a sense of humor!
The top ten worst suggestions commonly given to someone with a chronic...Handicap Parking and My Invisible Illness I have an invisible illness. To look at me you would see a short, fat, middle-aged grandmother. Sometimes I walk with a...When You're Not Sick EnoughBefore I even get started with this article, let me state for the record, that for those who have been approved for shor...Pay no attention to the girl behind the smile -what I wish people knew about me.Pay no attention to the girl behind the smile...
It has been said by many people that I am a very good actress. "But ...
Featured Video
ALL CATEGORIESALL CATEGORIES
Select Category
Articles  (571)
Caregiver Support and Tips  (18)
Daily Living Tips  (31)
Guest Writers  (65)
Hobbies and Crafts  (46)
1 day quick projects  (7)
Baking  (5)
Hobbies, Fun, Crafts  (7)
Ongoing Crafts and Projects  (5)
Seasonal Craft Projects  (15)
Lupus Information  (18)
Medical/ Heath Related  (12)
Personal Essays  (56)
Poetry  (34)
Seasonal Tips  (40)
Sick Humor  (29)
Spoon Lady Speaks  (111)
Tid Bits to Share  (13)
Tips and Articles  (55)
Top Ten Lists  (11)
Travel  (4)
Uncategorized  (24)
Website Reviews  (27)
written by Christine  (23)
written by Janet  (11)
Interviews  (8)
Book and Product Reviews  (406)
Book Reviews  (150)
Biographies and Autobiographies  (8)
Fiction  (19)
Health  (47)
Motivational / Inspirational  (8)
Mystery  (3)
Parenting/ Family Life  (9)
Reference / Textbook  (9)
Science Fiction/ Fantasy  (7)
Self Help  (7)
Spirituality / Religion  (1)
Product Reviews  (263)
Adaptive Clothing  (4)
Adaptive Devices  (6)
Aromatherapy Products  (7)
Baby products  (17)
Beauty/ Spa  (8)
Cleaning Helpers  (9)
Clothing and Accessories  (7)
Computer, Technology and Gadgets  (13)
Cosmetics  (4)
Daily Living Aids  (17)
Exercise Products  (3)
Gift Suggestions  (28)
Health Related  (28)
Health Related Products  (5)
Heating Pads and Ice Packs  (12)
Helpful Cooking Gadget Reviews  (13)
In the Kitchen  (14)
Lotions, Creams, and Skincare Products  (7)
Massage Products  (4)
Medical ID Bracelets  (4)
Medical Info / Links  (7)
Memory Foam Mattress Reviews  (3)
Mobility Aids  (3)
Music/ CD’s  (1)
Natural Pain Releiving Products  (5)
Online Shopping  (13)
Pet Products  (1)
Products for the Home  (8)
Safety  (3)
Sleep Aids  (14)
Sun Block and Skin Protection  (1)
Sun Protection  (2)
TV and Movie Reviews  (32)
Work From Home  (3)
Health Resources  (78)
Cooking/ Recipes  (49)
Crock Pot Recipes  (1)
Easy 1 Step Recipes  (12)
Special Diet/ Allergy Recipes  (9)
Healthy Foods  (29)
Philanthropy  (13)
The Spoon Theory  (6)
Press Releases  (23)
Videos  (8)
Upcoming Events  (5)
xMedia / Press  (24)
xSupport This Site  (4)
xAbout Us  (18)
Contests  (1)
Featured  (3)
Forums  (1)
Adaptive Aids, Mobility Aids, and Product Reviews  (1)
Allergies and Food Intolerances  (1)
Announcements  (1)
Arthritis  (1)
BYDLS Admin Chat  (1)
BYDLS Moderator Chat  (1)
Baby Boomers/ 50+/ Seniors  (1)
But You Don’t Look Sick?  (1)
ButYouDontLookSick.com Discussions  (1)
Cancer  (1)
Caregiver Support  (1)
Celebrations  (1)
Chat Room Hosts  (1)
Chronic Fatigue, Fibromyalgia and Chronic Myofascial Pain  (1)
Complementary / Alternative Therapies  (1)
Contests  (1)
Crafts and Hobbies  (1)
Depression/Mental Illness  (1)
Diabetes and Blood Sugar  (1)
Digestive Disorders  (1)
Doctors and Hospitals, etc.  (1)
Eating Disorders  (1)
Ehlers Danlos Syndrome EDS & HyperMobility Syndrome GHS  (1)
Family And Friends  (1)
Fun and Games  (1)
Going To School/ University  (1)
Graphic Designers  (1)
Guest Writers  (1)
Happy Hour  (1)
Having a Bad Day / Venting  (1)
Headaches, Migraines, etc.  (1)
Healthy Weight Management  (1)
Heart Conditions inc Dysautonomia  (1)
In the News…  (1)
Infertility and Health Related Fertility Issues.  (1)
Invisible Diseases  (1)
Links, Awards and More!  (1)
Love, Dating, and Marriage  (1)
Lupus  (1)
Lyme Disease  (1)
Medications  (1)
Multiple Sclerosis  (1)
Neurological Diseases  (1)
New Members – Say Hello  (1)
Pain Management  (1)
Parenting/Family LIfe  (1)
Pet Therapy  (1)
Philanthropy and Fundraising  (1)
Photo Section  (1)
Publicity/ PR  (1)
Rare and Orphan Illnesses  (1)
Recently Diagnosed  (1)
Secondary Medical Issues  (1)
Side Effects  (1)
Sjogrens Syndrome  (1)
Sleep Disorders and Insomnia  (1)
Social Butterflies  (1)
Social Security Benefits  (1)
Special Projects  (1)
Spiritual Support  (1)
Spoon Stories  (1)
Tests And Procedures  (1)
The Diner  (1)
Thyroid and Endocrine Disorders  (1)
Tips of the Trade  (1)
Topic Of The Week  (1)
Undiagnosed  (1)
Unlisted  (1)
Volunteer bydls.com staff work room  (1)
Work From Home Spoonies  (1)
Work Related  (1)
Young Adults /teens and 20 Somethings  (1)
ButYouDontLookSick.com ARCHIVES ButYouDontLookSick.com ARCHIVES
Select Month
May 2016  (3)
April 2016  (4)
July 2015  (1)
October 2014  (3)
August 2014  (3)
July 2014  (3)
April 2013  (7)
March 2013  (5)
December 2012  (6)
November 2012  (5)
September 2012  (5)
August 2012  (1)
July 2012  (3)
June 2012  (2)
May 2012  (1)
April 2012  (3)
March 2012  (4)
February 2012  (7)
January 2012  (9)
December 2011  (8)
November 2011  (3)
October 2011  (9)
September 2011  (8)
August 2011  (17)
July 2011  (17)
June 2011  (9)
May 2011  (16)
April 2011  (25)
March 2011  (23)
February 2011  (29)
January 2011  (13)
December 2010  (4)
November 2010  (11)
October 2010  (14)
September 2010  (23)
August 2010  (12)
July 2010  (19)
June 2010  (15)
May 2010  (23)
April 2010  (14)
March 2010  (14)
February 2010  (1)
January 2010  (6)
June 2009  (1)
May 2009  (13)
April 2009  (9)
March 2009  (4)
February 2009  (3)
January 2009  (13)
December 2008  (23)
November 2008  (20)
October 2008  (20)
September 2008  (28)
August 2008  (24)
July 2008  (19)
June 2008  (19)
May 2008  (32)
April 2008  (20)
March 2008  (17)
February 2008  (25)
January 2008  (30)
December 2007  (15)
November 2007  (21)
October 2007  (18)
September 2007  (13)
August 2007  (19)
July 2007  (11)
June 2007  (6)
May 2007  (10)
April 2007  (14)
March 2007  (5)
February 2007  (8)
January 2007  (9)
December 2006  (8)
November 2006  (24)
October 2006  (14)
September 2006  (9)
August 2006  (14)
July 2006  (14)
June 2006  (12)
May 2006  (9)
April 2006  (7)
March 2006  (13)
February 2006  (10)
January 2006  (5)
December 2005  (2)
November 2005  (71)
October 2005  (4)
August 2005  (6)
Disclaimer: The owners and authors of this site do not promote, support, or recommend any particular website, product, treatment or medication for any medical condition. No treatment should be undertaken without the supervision of a physician.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Disclosure Policy
© ButYouDontLookSick.com
